Jhala said
that in their previous
trade today, we observed the market going up.
With this, we will see
how the market can fit in the future. So let's start.
First of all, let's talk about the market coming up. In the
market, we saw a
lot of
short covering in Nifty and Bank Nifty. Or we were
remembering 2008 and 1%,
due to which we
see another comment in our market. The
other day, it was removed. Futures, this top
price, after yesterday's protest, had broken 1310 points.
So, or because of the Chinese real
estate, Everest Group from Karachi,
which is the biggest property
developer, due to this, the trend here is
quite negative. But because of its
features side, we can see a recovery. So,
it has a positive impact.
Today, when the market is looking at the downside,
we can look at 108 companies in some sectors,
which include capital
goods, oil and gas, IT and realty.
Some of these stocks are being
talked about by the stock market.  And in these
and on that, we
see that there is no role of a bill in
today's market place, so the guide is
downloading almost here, and even now the
S&P 500 and Nasdaq, we
see a lot of solid strength here. If we pay this tax, if
we do 17500 and at least some
support from the back soil, then you can
make stars here from any actress, soldier funny, and buy only when the
level here is only 10. Here
we can see the heading as per the free here,
as in the last two days, after a few staff,
today the market almost
opened, after this, due to a website,
we have developed it to 7503 - unknown, nothing for now,
if we develop, then here below here,
black clothes, a little bit of a
good writing has come, and above we
can see another unwanted here,
this is quite difficult for you, but as long as
we are above the basic crossing of 7528
You don't need to do much panic selling in the
morning. If the market closes at
1768 tomorrow, only then will you have to
click on Indramani Gautam and you
can sell at the option verified at 17500. In this case, even for buying,
750 call trading will be an option because
after that, you will see the market moving up a
little bit here.
If we talk about gas, then
today we will see a portion of one or two G in it.
Because
after a big rock, we have again
clicked on 370 here, so right now
alosing
3000 will work as a fan for us. So guys,
now the speed
is that handsfree, I can't say that nothing worked out in this,
we can confirm this with the vibrator here.
If you can see in these gestures, there are
benefits here,
as you can see here, so at this
time there is a good foot writing on the top of the achieved
and special poet of oil change, there is a
little bit of call center time in it.  So,
until the many calls arranged below here are
not unwinded, the
market will consolidate here.
After that, until we do not see 37500, then I will do
more trading in it
and if you are doing it for the first time, then there is a
lot of cigarette here,
you can see a little cross here above,
then there is a call someone and until we
are above 37500, we have to refrain from creating any fresh
long position in it.
If we talk about some stocks,
tomorrow we can see a trading office
meeting in it, the
first of which is West Indies-England. Because of this,
today we can see a very calm recovery in the market.
Provided that the
stock had corrected as much as it had in the last two days,
after today's volume line, the
selling pressure has completely subsided
and now we will see shares above 150 here,
that gas, you can take at least a shortcoming
of ₹50 in it
or it will exit, we will spend
our time in it.  1154 1125 plus and which
we will see when it becomes cheaper above 1135,
comments from the body of our plant and after this the
next topic is a recent list five
and here we can see that the excise duty
price today strike for the first time here its
100 how many
rings here what is the film and
looking at this now if we re-check this look tomorrow at our time then
you are a pray
in this at least three to ₹50 an off side can be
seen in it so guide a little
120 can work as a trigger for us on
this we can chill quality 138 10
glasses such tight type
so before moving ahead in this video, if
you liked the video then please like it and
subscribe to the channel because
it gives us a lot of motivation
how you are
in giving important updates so rider third
stock this oil which was
like the previous friends in this we get
to see iTunes five interest and it can also be seen
played once  It is possible that after the
Jatropha that came in it after Friday, for the
first time we get to see a used
by interest received pan in it, so
guys if we can go above 1100 then
you have
added more in it and
if we do it above the fourth,
we have
seen profit booking in it today,
seeing which now tomorrow again
if you see fire in a pond below the note, then
you can
see up to ₹2 being booked in it, due to that
we are afraid,
you can get fixed and defaulter plus on
which you can get an officer for profit booking here,
how much is there in this video for 68 in the morning, so see you
in the next video and if you have
not yet subscribed to our Telegram channel then do
go and those who are here for
swimming related updates, we have our bullet
which should be turned on, definitely share it and
for access to model flowers, you will find the link and
details below, till we go, see you
in the next video and 531 has happened